<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>home</title>
    
    
    <description>This website is proof that we&apos;re interested in everything to do with technology, and that we&apos;re always on the lookout for new innovations and advances in science.</description>
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Leveraging Multiple AIs for Reliable Research and Content Creation</title>
        <description>
          A Step-by-Step Guide to Combining American, Chinese, and French AI Tools for Comprehensive Results - 
          In today’s digital landscape, artificial intelligence is not only changing the way we work but also how we search for, consolidate, and present information. This guide explains a method that combines several AI tools from different parts of the world to help you obtain objective, reliable, and comprehensive answers. By...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-05-04-KAPTAN-DATA-SOLUTIONS-ITEMS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-05-04-KAPTAN-DATA-SOLUTIONS-ITEMS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unlocking Autonomous Automation - A How‑To Guide on AI Agents</title>
        <description>
          Enhance Your Workflows with Intelligent Agents That Decide, Act, and Learn - 
          In today’s fast‑paced digital landscape, automation tools are evolving. New intelligent agents are shifting the way we think about workflow automation—moving from rigid, pre‑defined scenarios to dynamic systems that can decide, act, and even learn from context. In this guide, we explain how to leverage these AI agents to build...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-05-04-KAPTAN-DATA-SOLUTIONS-ITEMS-1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-05-04-KAPTAN-DATA-SOLUTIONS-ITEMS-1/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Top 10 Tech News of the Week</title>
        <description>
          Cutting-Edge Innovations Fueling the Future of Tech - 
          Top 10 Tech News of the Week: AI in the Spotlight The world of technology continues to evolve at breakneck speed. In this week’s roundup, we explore ten major happenings that are shaping the future of artificial intelligence, mobile ecosystems, and digital transformation. Dive into each story below as we...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-05-03-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-05-03-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Top 10 Tech Developments Shaping Digital Sovereignty and AI Advancements</title>
        <description>
          The trends that will shape your data, code and business projects over the next 12 months - 
          🔝 Top 10 Tech News - April 28, 2025 1. Generative AI-Powered Language Tutoring Context. The language edtech market already weighs $29B and is growing at 18%/year. Platforms are looking to move from a static subscription model to a log in-loop based on the real value provided in each session....
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-04-28-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-04-28-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Top 10 Tech Developments Shaping Digital Sovereignty and AI Advancements</title>
        <description>
          This week, explore critical insights into antitrust cases involving Google and Meta, revolutionary AI models from OpenAI, the future of blockchain and sovereign clouds, and significant regulatory challenges - 
          🔝 Top 10 Tech News - April 22, 2025 1. ⚖️ Google found guilty of antitrust violations in the United States The U.S. federal court has found Google guilty of intentionally manipulating its automated advertising bidding system (ATEC), significantly restricting competition. This verdict could potentially lead to a partial dismantling...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-04-22-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-04-22-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Harness the Power of AI Without Internet Access</title>
        <description>
          Secure, Customizable, and Efficient Solutions for Your Enterprise - 
          In today’s competitive environment, ensuring data security, efficiency, and compliance is paramount. At [Your Company Name], we specialize in delivering advanced Artificial Intelligence (AI) solutions specifically designed to operate entirely offline, fully integrated within your existing IT infrastructure. Discover our tailored, secure, and efficient AI solutions—crafted to boost your productivity...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-04-20-harness_the_power_of_ai/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-04-20-harness_the_power_of_ai/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Podcast - Agent2Agent (A2A) Protocol for Enhanced AI Agent Collaboration</title>
        <description>
          Unlocking AI Potential through Open and Seamless Interoperability - 
          A2A: An Innovative Protocol for Open Agent Collaboration The rapid advancement of artificial intelligence (AI) has led to an increasing proliferation of applications based on autonomous agents. These agents, systems capable of performing tasks autonomously or semi-autonomously, have become essential in managing the growing complexity of digital systems. However, collaboration...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-04-14-A2A-protocol/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-04-14-A2A-protocol/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>AI at Your Fingertips - How Local AI Solutions Empower Confidential Data Management</title>
        <description>
          Empowering Confidential Data Management with Secure, Locally Hosted AI Solutions - 
          AI without the Internet: GPT-4 on Your Private Server, Secured and Confidential [See the demo on our website] The rise of ChatGPT and GPT-4 has revolutionized how we leverage artificial intelligence (AI). However, organizations handling sensitive data often hesitate to use online AI services because it involves transmitting confidential information...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-03-31-Local-IA/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-03-31-Local-IA/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Top 10 Tech News of the Week</title>
        <description>
          Manus AI, Apple&apos;s Challenges, Cybersecurity, Digital Health, Organic Computing, and More. - 
          KAP10 Weekly: Top 10 Latest Tech News Welcome to this week’s episode of KAP10 Weekly! Here’s a detailed overview of the top 10 tech news stories, enriched with additional insights and analyses. Here is the news for March 17, 2025 1. Manus, the AI Revolution from China The Chinese startup...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-03-17-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-03-17-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Top 10 Tech News of the Week</title>
        <description>
          This week, discover the technological advances shaping our future - from AI in smartphones to connected glasses, private 5G networks and new revolutions in mobile photography. - 
          Every week, KAP10 takes you to the heart of innovations transforming our world. Discover the latest advances, significant trends, and emerging technologies that will shape our future. To stay at the cutting edge, follow all our news on KaptanDataSolutions.github.io! Here is the news for March 10, 2025 Fast Internet Connection...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-03-10-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-03-10-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Top 10 Tech News of the Week</title>
        <description>
          From Alexa Plus to Quantum Chips - A Roundup of This Week&apos;s Top Tech Innovations - 
          Top 10 Tech News (March 3, 2025) 1. Alexa Plus: Amazon’s Voice Assistant Reinvented Amazon takes a giant leap forward with Alexa Plus. This new version of the intelligent assistant now incorporates generative AI, enabling it to engage in more natural conversations—with hesitations and nuances reminiscent of human exchanges. According...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-03-03-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-03-03-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Top 10 Tech News of the Week</title>
        <description>
          Exploring DeepSeek&apos;s Rise, OpenAI&apos;s Operator, Quantum Advances in France, and Breakthroughs in AI Energy Efficiency - 
          Top 10 Tech News from Monde Numérique (February 1, 2025) 1. DeepSeek: The Chinese AI Challenging American Giants DeepSeek, an artificial intelligence developed in China, is shaking up the industry. It offers performance comparable to ChatGPT while being significantly more cost-effective, making it a formidable competitor to Western leaders. However,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-02-03-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-02-03-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Top 10 Tech News of the Week - AI in the Spotlight</title>
        <description>
          Exploring the Stargate Project, OpenAI&apos;s Operator, Mistral AI, Samsung&apos;s Galaxy S25, and breakthroughs in AI energy efficiency - 
          Top 10 Tech News of the Week: AI in the Spotlight This week, the tech world has been buzzing with major announcements, particularly in the field of artificial intelligence (AI). Here’s our selection of the 10 most notable stories, spanning innovations, geopolitics, and digital transformation. 1. Stargate Project: A Record-Breaking...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-01-27-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-01-27-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Major Tech and Digital Trends of the Moment</title>
        <description>
          Exploring TikTok&apos;s American drama, AI revolutions, Big Tech vs. EU regulations, and humanoid robotics - 
          The Major Tech and Digital Trends of the Moment: What You Need to Know In a constantly evolving world, technology continues to shape our lives and interactions. On this January 20, 2025, several major events have marked the digital landscape, with significant implications for geopolitics, the economy, and our societies....
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-01-21-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-01-21-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Key Trends and Technological News of the Moment</title>
        <description>
          A deep dive into CES 2025, AI breakthroughs, USB-C standardization, and privacy challenges - 
          Key Trends and Technological News of the Moment 1. Explosion of a Tesla Cybertruck in Las Vegas On January 1, 2025, a Tesla Cybertruck exploded in front of the Trump International Hotel in Las Vegas. The incident, caused by a U.S. soldier who committed suicide, resulted in several injuries. The...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2025-01-06-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2025-01-06-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - Apple and Samsung Revolutionize Foldable Displays and Extended Reality</title>
        <description>
          A comprehensive overview of the latest technological advancements in foldable displays, extended reality, and artificial intelligence - 
          Introduction Welcome to this edition of KAP10 Weekly Update, where we delve into the latest technological advancements shaping our world. This week, we explore innovations from Apple and Samsung in foldable displays and extended reality, developments in artificial intelligence at Google DeepMind, as well as the European Union’s space initiatives....
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-12-18-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-12-18-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update – Massive Investments, AI Browsers, and Industry Shake-Ups</title>
        <description>
          Detailed Insights on the Latest Developments in AI, Smartphones, and Corporate Governance - 
          Meta Invests $10 Billion in Submarine Cable Network Meta announced a $10 billion investment to build a 40,000 km fiber-optic submarine cable network. Nicknamed “W” for its shape, this network will connect the East and West coasts of the U.S., India, South Africa, and Australia. It deliberately avoids geopolitically sensitive...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-12-08-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-12-08-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update – Major Cyberattacks, AI Innovations, and Tech Industry Legal Challenges</title>
        <description>
          An In-Depth Analysis of This Week&apos;s Significant Developments in Cybersecurity, Artificial Intelligence, and Legal Affairs in the Tech Industry - 
          Cyberattack on SFR Exposes Millions of Subscribers’ Data On November 24, 2024, the hacker group Near2tlg claimed responsibility for a cyberattack on French telecom operator SFR, alleging the theft of personal data from 3.6 million subscribers. The compromised information includes names, addresses, birth dates, and phone numbers. Initially, the group...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-11-30-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-11-30-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>KAP10 Weekly Update - OpenAI Web Search, Freds Growth, and Controversial Changes on X</title>
        <description>
          A Deep Dive into This Week’s Major Developments in AI Integration, Social Media Expansion, and Tech Policy Shifts - 
          OpenAI Integrates Real-Time Web Search in ChatGPT OpenAI has integrated real-time web search into ChatGPT, enabling the chatbot to access up-to-date information and compete effectively with its competitors. Initially available for paying subscribers and those on a waitlist, this feature will be gradually rolled out to all users in the...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-11-22-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-11-22-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Technological News: Snowflake Intelligence, Cloudera Acquisition, and AI Advancements</title>
        <description>
          An overview of recent developments in data science, physics, and health - 
          Technological News in Data Science, Physics, and Health Recent developments in data science, physics, and health highlight significant initiatives and trends: Snowflake Launches Snowflake Intelligence Snowflake, a company specializing in cloud data for AI, announced “Snowflake Intelligence,” a new platform enabling businesses to easily ask business questions across all their...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2024-11-18-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2024-11-18-KAP-TEN-LAST-TECH-NEWS/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
